## **Dmitriy Zatulovskiy**

Front End Developer, UI/UX Designer, HTML Layout maker

- s grafsoul
- @GrafSoul
- 🄰 @GrafSoul in Linkedin/DZ
- github.com/GrafSoul
- grafsoul.github.io
- networkroom.ru
- ⇔ CodePen/NetWorkRoom

#### **EDUCATION Junior Engineer**

**Tashkent Radio Engineering** Technical School 1987 - 1990 **UX Developer** 

GeekBrains 2018

**Front End Developer** Udacity 2020

### **LANGUAGES**

English (Professional)

Russian (Native)

#### **INTERESTS** Programming

Visual Arts

Reading books

Music

Movies, Serials

Bicycling

## CAREER PROFILE

My name is Dmitriy Zatulovskiy. I was born in 1972, and I am 48 years old. I started my professional career in 1996. I was designing and implementing computer networks for several years. Since 1999, I was worked in the field of print design and advertising, for almost 12 years. In the last place, I was held the position of art director. For the last 9 years, I have been engaged in web development, as a designer, HTML and CSS coder and JavaScript programmer. I work as a freelancer.

## Below is a list of web apps I've made in the last three years.

WEB APPS PROJECTS

**VID.OK** - Simple example of using WebRTC technology to create a video chat. **PAINT.OK** - Example of an app for drawing and communicating together.

READ.OK - Simple app for speech synthesis using React.js and Speech Synthesis API.

**DICT.OK** - Simple app for Speech to Text using React.js and Web Speech API.

**SAY.OK** - Example of building a Chat using React.js and Socket.io.

**IntoPoint** - Application for storing links to sites, notes, code, and viewing news.

## Below is a list of Windows desktop apps I've made in the last three years.

**Radion** - Applications for listening to the broadcast of radio stations.

**Talker** - Applications for reading text with a voice engine.

**CHROME APPS PROJECTS** 

**SKILLS & PROFICIENCY** 





WebSockets Socket.IO WebRTC Desktop and Mobile **Android Studio** Expo **React Native React Navigation** 

and Debugging Postman Chrome DevTools **Jasmine** Jest Redux DevTools Apollo Client DevTools Vue.js devtools

#### Freelancer I design interfaces for web services, design corporate websites, landing pages for services and products, and online stores. I create SPA applications on ReactJS and VueJS.

EXPERIENCES

Front End Developer,

**HTML Layout maker** 

UI/UX Designer,

WebSockets and WebRTC

**Testing** 

Designer "SM-Alliance", Tashkent

worked on the development of advertising campaigns, signage, stands for retail outlets, as well as the design of stores. I was preparing for the printing of advertising layouts for printing in the media, as well as outdoor advertising placed on advertising structures in the city. I was engaged

in the production of flash banners to inform about promotions and new products via the Internet.

Performed work on the promotion of LG and AOC products on the market. As a designer, I

**Art director** 2009 "DiPLUS", Tashkent The main responsibilities were the development of a new design of the newspaper and its implementation, layout design, design of articles, preparation of photos and illustrations for printing in offset printing, work with printing houses, print quality control, organization of work

Art director 2008 - 2009

articles, preparation of photos and illustrations for printing in offset printing, work with printing houses, print quality control, organization of work with the magazine's photographers, providing technical support for the publication. I was responsible for all the technical and artistic processes

with photographers, providing technical support. I was responsible for all the technical and

I worked in the magazine "Careerist" as an art director. The main responsibilities were the development and implementation of the main concept of the magazine, layout design, design of

Web Designer 2007 - 2010 "LIS International Design.", Irvin, USA I have carried out orders for the development of website design, as well as corporate identity for various companies that are clients of LIS International Design. Designer 2007

I was performed the design and layout of the project's mailing for e-mail, as well as the design and

layout of monthly reports. Designer

"NCI Projects Inc.", Tashkent

"BAS Programme (EBRD)", Tashkent

inside the magazine's editorial office.

worked on the design of the advertising platform at the Kitel 2002 exhibition (in Kazakhstan), participated in the development of an electronic textbook on the Russian language (junior

classes) for the Ministry of Public Education of Uzbekistan. He was engaged in the development

Designer and Flash Maker 2003 "MFD-InfoCenter.", Moscow I carried out orders for the production of banners for online advertising campaigns. Developed

#### Designer and Art director Center for Economic Research.

publications, also performing work on layout, design, production of advertising original layouts, retouching and preparing photos for printing. I was responsible for all the technical and artistic processes inside the magazine's editorial office. **Engineer and Project manager** 1996 - 1998

I worked as a project manager in the field of computer network technologies, and also led a group

#### engaged in the development of web sites and the production of advertising original layouts for the company's clients.

000 "Olsoft", Tashkent

## **List of certificates**

## **Udacity**

- 1.) Certificate Nanodegree Program Front End Web Developer. 2.) Certificate Nanodegree Program - Android Development Track.
- 3.) Certificate Nanodegree Program Front End Development Track.
- 4.) Certificate Nanodegree Program Full Stack Development Track.
- a personal website.

# WINDOWS DESKTOP APPS PROJECTS

**Reco** - Video and audio recording application.

WrappS - Shell for using various audio and video services. **Voice Clock** - Voice clock app for voice notification of the current time.

**Tempus** - A simple application to work with time.

**Dictantor** - App for converting voice to text.

**VueJS Vue Router** Vuex **Vue SSR NuxtJS** 

> **ElectronJS** React DevTools

> > 2011 - Present time

2010 - 2011

2002 - 2005

1999 - 2008

artistic processes inside the newspaper's editorial office. "Career Press", Tashkent

I was worked on the creation of a corporate website and its support and promotion (banners, screensavers, wallpapers). I also did office design work (booklets, folders, pens, notepads). I

of the corporate identity of the company "Soft Engineer" (Kazakhstan.).

and prepared to print the elements of the office design.

(UNDP project "Social and Economic Development of Uzbekistan"), Tashkent I worked in the magazine "Economic Review", published by the Center, headed the department of

## **CERTIFICATES**

- **GeekBrains**
- 1.) Certificate Design the user interface . UI/UX. 2.) Certificate - Website development on your own-intensive Web Development Training. Creating

© 2021 | Dmitriy Zatulovskiy

3.) Certificate - Intensive Introduction to Programming. Online course. Certificate - Fundamentals of database.